$SLA_Settings	Settings
$SLA_Status	Status
$SLA_PuppetMaster	Puppet Master
$SLA_StatusNotSplash	Show status instead of splash page
$SLA_StatusNotSplashInfo	Show status page instead of splash screen image.
$SLA_PlayerStatus	Player Status Information
$SLA_NpcStatus	NPC Status Information
$SLA_SelectPuppet	Select puppet actor
$SLA_SelectPuppetInfo	Use this drop-down to select the target 'puppet' to manipulate. Choices may vary.
$SLA_Yes	Yes
$SLA_No	No
$SLA_CurrentArmorList	Current Equipment
$SLA_Naked	Naked
$SLA_Bikini	Bikini
$SLA_Sexy	Sexy
$SLA_Slooty	Slooty
$SLA_Illegal	Illegal
$SLA_Posh	Respectable
$SLA_Ragged	Ragged
$SLA_KillerHeelsList	Killer Heels
$SLA_EnableDetails	Enable detailed options
$SLA_SelectActor	Select target actor
$SLA_EquippedItems	Equipped Items
$SLA_Options	Options
$SLA_BodyItem	Body item
$SLA_NoBodyItem	No body item
$SLA_ShoesBoots	Shoes/Boots
$SLA_NoShoesBoots	No boots or shoes
$SLA_HighHeels	High Heels
$SLA_TargetActorMenuInfo	Use this to pick the target actor to select clothing/armor items from. You can always pick the player, but sometimes other actors may be available to pick.
$SLA_SliderModeInfo	Enable to set clothing properties from 0 to 100 using sliders, rather than simple toggle controls. Disable to use the simple/quick toggle controls.
$SLA_BodyItemInfo	This is the item in your 'Body' slot (slot 32). This is the primary slot used by mods to determine the properties of your current outfit. Change its type using the controls on the right.
$SLA_NoBodyItemInfo	No item is equipped in your 'Body' slot (slot 32). If this is empty, mods will usually consider you to be naked, even if you are wearing other items that *appear* to cover the body.
$SLA_NakedSliderInfo	Set the extent to which this item is equivalent to naked. 0 means not naked at all. Any non-zero value is usually considered NOT naked, but some mods may perform a threshold check, or use the value to scale effects.
$SLA_BikiniSliderInfo	Set the extent to which this item is considered a bikini part. 0 means not a bikini at all. Any non-zero value is usually considered a bikini, but some mods may perform a threshold check, or scale effects by value.
$SLA_SexySliderInfo	Set the extent to which this item is considered sexy: an item that is pleasantly attractive to others, not necessarily lewd or erotic. 0 means not sexy at all. Any non-zero value is usually considered sexy. Some mods may perform a threshold check, or use the value to scale effects.
$SLA_SlootySliderInfo	Set the extent to which this item is considered slooty: an item that is overty erotic and sexualised. 0 means not erotic at all. Any non-zero value is usually considered slooty. Some mods may perform a threshold check, or use the value to scale effects.
$SLA_IllegalSliderInfo	Set the extent to which this item is considered illegal: an item that may result in fines, confiscations, or arrests. 0 means not illegal at all. Any non-zero value is usually illegal, but higher values may attract a more extreme penalty.
$SLA_PoshSliderInfo	Set the extent to which this item indicates high status and inspires respect or better treatment. 0 means not at all. Any non-zero value is usually considered worthy of respect. Some mods may perform a threshold check, or use the value to scale effects.
$SLA_RaggedSliderInfo	Set the extent to which this item is ragged, indicating poverty and low status. It may result contempt or pity. 0 means not ragged at all. Any non-zero value is usually considered ragged. Some mods may perform a threshold check, or use the value to scale effects.
$SLA_NakedToggleInfo	Toggle whether the worn item is equivalent to being naked or not. If enabled it sets a naked value of 51. If disabled, it sets a value of 0. Any non-zero value is usually considered to be the same as being naked.
$SLA_BikiniToggleInfo	Toggle whether the worn item is part of a bikini or not. If enabled it sets a bikini value of 51. If disabled, it sets a value of 0. Any non-zero value usually means the item is part of a bikini.
$SLA_SexyToggleInfo	Toggle whether the worn item is sexy or not. In this case, sexy means attractive to others, but not necessarily lewd or erotic. If enabled it sets a sexy value of 51. If disabled, it sets a value of 0. Any non-zero value usually means the item is sexy.
$SLA_SlootyToggleInfo	Toggle whether the worn item is slooty or not. In this case, slooty means obviously erotic and sexualised. Some may consider it obscene. If enabled it sets a slooty value of 51. If disabled, it sets a value of 0. Any non-zero value usually means the item is slooty.
$SLA_IllegalToggleInfo	Toggle whether the worn item is illegal or not. Illegal means deserving of fines or arrest (or confiscation) if worn in public. If enabled it sets an illegal value of 51. If disabled, it set a value of 0. Any non-zero value usually means the item is illegal.
$SLA_PoshToggleInfo	Toggle whether the worn item is respectable or not. This means rich clothing that is a visual indicator of wealth and power. If enabled it sets a respectable value of 51. If disabled, it sets a value of 0. Any non-zero value usually means the item is respectable.
$SLA_RaggedToggleInfo	Toggle whether the worn item is ragged or not. This means poor clothing that is a visual indicator of poverty and low status. It may result in pity, or contempt. If enabled it sets a ragged value of 51. If disabled, it sets a value of 0. Any non-zero value usually means the item is ragged.
$SLA_FootItemInfo	This is the item in your 'Feet' slot (slot 37). This is the primary slot used by mods to find what boots or shoes the character is wearing. You can set whether they are high heels using the control to the right.
$SLA_NoFootItemInfo	No item is equipped in your 'Feet' slot (slot 37). This is the primary slot used by mods to find what boots or shoes the character is wearing. If empty you will probably be detected as having bare feet.
$SLA_HeelsSliderInfo	Set the extent to which this footwear is considered to have 'high heels', such as stilletos, platforms, or anything else that is harder to walk in and less comfortable than thin flat soles. 0 means no high heels. 100 would suggest extreme bedroom-only heels.
$SLA_HeelsToggleInfo	Toggle whether the footwear has obvious high heels, such as stilletos, platforms, or anything else that is harder to walk in and less comfortable than thin flat soles. If enabled is sets a value of 75. If disabled it sets a value of 0. Any non-zero value is considered to indicate high heels.
$SLA_Male	Male
$SLA_Female	Female
$SLA_Both	Both
$SLA_UseSexLab	Use SexLab Sexuality
$SLA_Version	Version :
$SLA_General	General
$SLA_StatusKey	Status Notification Key
$SLA_InfoStatusKey	Change key that displays arousal status.\nHold key for more then 2.0 seconds to release arousal.\nDefault: 'N'
$SLA_EnableDesire	Enable Desire Spell
$SLA_InfoDesire	Adds Lover's Desire spell to player, effects vary according to arousal level.\nDefault: TRUE
$SLA_ExtendedNPCNaked	Naked Armor for NPC
$SLA_InfoExtendedNPCNaked	If true then custom naked armor is also checked for NPC, but creates more stress on papyrus.\nIf false works only for PC. Default: FALSE
$SLA_EnableSOS	Enable SOS
$SLA_InfoEnableSOS	If enabled arousal would effect schlong state.\nEnable only if SOS is installed. Default: FALSE
$SLA_Arousal	Arousal
$SLA_ArousalBlocked	Is Arousal Blocked
$SLA_InfoBlockedArousal	If set to TRUE then PC/NPC arousal will always be -2.\nDefault: FALSE
$SLA_ArousalLocked	Is Arousal Locked
$SLA_InfoLockedArousal	After is set to TRUE then PC/NPC arousal will not change, even if exposure and time would change.\nDefault: FALSE
$SLA_GenderPreference	Gender Preference
$SLA_InfoGenderPreference	Select PC/NPC gender preference.\nDefault: Use SexLab Sexuality (For Ostim this option will default to Both)
$SLA_IsExhibitionist	Is Exhibitionist
$SLA_InfoIsExhibitionist	If set true PC/NPC gets aroused if somebody see him/her naked.\nDefault: FALSE
$SLA_ArousalLevel	Arousal = Sum of all effects
$SLA_NotificationArousal20	My desires are satisfied
$SLA_NotificationArousal20Rape	My desires are gone
$SLA_NotificationArousal90	My desires are driving me...
$SLA_NotificationArousal70	I need to have sex
$SLA_NotificationArousal50	I have difficulty focusing...
$SLA_ESMDistracted	Distracted
$SLA_ESMSatisfied	Satisfied
$SLA_ESMAroused	Aroused
$SLA_ESMNeedSex	Need Sex
$SLA_ESMLosingControl	Losing Control
$SLA_ESMLAddicted	Addicted
$SLA_CellScanFreq	Cell Scan Frequency Seconds
$SLA_InfoCellScanFreq	How often to scan for aroused actors\nDefault 120 seconds
$SLA_WantsPurging	Purge Dead Actors Every 5 Game Days
$SLA_WantsPurgingDesc	If this item is checked on, a purge is started and repeated every 5 game days.\nPurging removes old Arousal data for actors which haven't been updated at least 10 days otherwise.
$SLA_EnableMaleAnimation	Enable Male Aroused Animations
$SLA_EnableMaleAnimationDesc	If this is checked on, male actors will play aroused idles when their arousal is above the threshold (50)
$SLA_EnableFemaleAnimation	Enable Female Aroused Animations
$SLA_EnableFemaleAnimationDesc	If this is checked on, female actors will play aroused idles when their arousal is above the threshold (50)\n Note:Unfinished Leito Animation.  Looking for volunteer to finish this.
$SLA_UseLOS	Require Line of Sight for arousal.
$SLA_UseLOSDesc	Only actors that are looking at a naked actor at the time of the scan will have their arousal updated.
$SLA_IsNakedOnly	Require naked actors to change arousal.
$SLA_IsNakedOnlyDesc	If checked, actors arousal will only be updated if there is at least one naked actor.\nCheck to increase performance.  Some mods require this to be unchecked.
$SLA_Disabled	Aroused is disabled.
$SLA_DisabledDesc	If checked, Aroused is disabled and arousal is not computed.\nGood for stuff like big battles.  Other mods may still change arousal directly.
$SLA_MBonUsesSLGender	Use SexLab Gender
$SLA_EnableNotifications	Enable Notifications
$SLA_SmallUpdateCount	Small updates per full update
$SLA_SmallUpdateDesc	Number of small incremental updates between slower full update with LOS checks between nearby actors. 0 = feature disabled
$SLA_PluginList	Plugin List
$SLA_EffectSetting	Effect Settings
$SLA_UnusedEffect	<unused>
$SLA_ExportImport	Import/Export Settings
$SLA_Export	Export Settings
$SLA_Working	Working...
$SLA_Done	Done!
$SLA_Import	Import Settings
$SLA_AlwaysCheckOrgasm	Always check orgasm condition
$SLA_AlwaysCheckOrgasmDesc	If this option is disabled the check if a character can orgasm in a sexlab scene will be skipped when SLSO is installed or SeparateOrgasms is enabled.

$SLA_PluginFilter	Filter
$SLA_FilterShowAll	Show All
$SLA_Effect_NakedCat	Naked Effect
$SLA_Effect_TimedCat	Timed Effect
$SLA_Effect_LegacyCat	Legacy (Exposure) Effect
$SLA_Effect_SatisfactionCat	Satisfaction Effect
$SLA_Effect_SexCat	Sex Effect
$SLA_Effect_TraumaCat	Trauma Effect
$SLA_Effect_FatigueCat	Fatigue Effect
$SLA_Effect_DeviceCat	Devious Devices

$SLA_Effect_Naked	Naked Exposure
$SLA_Effect_NakedDesc	Seeing naked people increases arousal. This effect accounts for gender preference.
$SLA_Effect_NakedMax	Maximum Naked
$SLA_Effect_NakedMaxDesc	Maximum amount of arousal gained from seeing naked characters.
$SLA_Effect_NakedMaxNonPref	Maximum Naked (Non-Preffered)
$SLA_Effect_NakedMaxNonPrefDesc	Maximum amount of arousal gained from seeing naked non-preffered characters.
$SLA_Effect_NakedRate	Naked increase per actor
$SLA_Effect_NakedRateDesc	Arousal increase per hour per naked actor. Naked actors with preffered gender count twice.
$SLA_Effect_NakedHalfTime	Naked Half-Time
$SLA_Effect_NakedHalfTimeDesc	Time in ingame hours after which the arousal from the naked effect is halfed.

$SLA_Effect_Satisfaction	Satisfaction
$SLA_Effect_SatisfactionDesc	Reduces arousal after having an orgasm.

$SLA_Effect_Timed	Timed Arousal
$SLA_Effect_TimedDesc	Arousal increases after a long time without orgasm.
$SLA_Effect_TimedUseCycle	Use timed cycle
$SLA_Effect_TimedUseCycleDesc	Instead of becoming becoming succesivly more horny every character has a cycle
$SLA_Effect_TimedRate	Timed Rate
$SLA_Effect_TimedRateDesc	Average amount of arousal gained per day without orgasm.
$SLA_Effect_TimedMax	Maximum Timed arousal 
$SLA_Effect_TimedMaxDesc	Maximum amount of arousal gained from not having an orgasm.

$SLA_Effect_Legacy	Exposure (Legacy)
$SLA_Effect_LegacyDesc	Arousal from other mods using the legacy system.
$SLA_Effect_LegacyMultiplier	Legacy Exposure Rate
$SLA_Effect_LegacyMultiplierDesc	Multiplier for other mods which use the old exposure modifier.
$SLA_Effect_LegacyHalfTime	Legacy Exposure Half-Time
$SLA_Effect_LegacyHalfTimeDesc	Amount of hours needed for Exposure to reduce by half.\nIf Exposure is 10 with Decay Rate of 2, then after 2 hours Exposure would be 5.

$SLA_Effect_Sex	Sex Exposure
$SLA_Effect_SexDesc	Having sex or seeing people having sex increases arousal.
$SLA_Effect_SexMax	Maximum Sex Effect
$SLA_Effect_SexMaxDesc	Maximum amount of arousal gained from seeing characters having sex or participating in a sexlab scene.
$SLA_Effect_SexHalfTime	Sex Effect Half-Time
$SLA_Effect_SexHalfTimeDesc	Amount of hours needed for sex effect to reduce by half.
$SLA_Effect_SexPerStage	Arousal Per Stage
$SLA_Effect_SexPerStageDesc	Amount of arousal gained per Stage in a SexLab animation. Value is doubled in foreplay antimations.

$SLA_Effect_SatisfactionHalfTime	Satisfaction Half-Time
$SLA_Effect_SatisfactionHalfTimeDesc	Amount of hours needed for the satisfaction effect to reduce by half.
$SLA_Effect_SatisfactionBase	Base Satisfaction
$SLA_Effect_SatisfactionBaseDesc	Amount of arousal reduce gained by an orgasm
$SLA_Effect_SatisfactionRate	Satisfaction Rate
$SLA_Effect_SatisfactionRateDesc	Amount of arousal reduce gained per enjoyment
$SLA_Effect_SatisfactionFemaleRate	Satisfaction Female Rate
$SLA_Effect_SatisfactionFemaleRateDesc	Multiplier affecting the whole satisfaction effect (base + rate) for female characters

$SLA_Effect_Fatigue	Fatigue
$SLA_Effect_FatigueDesc	Fatigue decreases your arousal after every intercourse.
$SLA_Effect_FatigueHalfTime	Fatigue Half-Time
$SLA_Effect_FatigueHalfTimeDesc	Amount of days needed for the Fatigue effect to reduce by half. Changing this value to zero will disables the Fatigue effect.
$SLA_Effect_FatigueBase	Fatigue
$SLA_Effect_FatigueBaseDesc	Amount of arousal reduction after every intercourse. 

$SLA_Effect_Trauma	Trauma
$SLA_Effect_TraumaDesc	Being raped decreases your arousal except for very lewd characters.
$SLA_Effect_TraumaHalfTime	Trauma Half-Time
$SLA_Effect_TraumaHalfTimeDesc	Amount of days needed for the trauma effect to reduce by half. Changing this value to zero will disables the trauma effect.
$SLA_Effect_TraumaBase	Trauma Base Reduction
$SLA_Effect_TraumaBaseDesc	Base arousal reduction when a character has been raped. 
$SLA_Effect_TraumaLewd	Trauma Lewd Rate
$SLA_Effect_TraumaLewdDesc	Multiplier for arousal increase when a character has been raped based on SexLab lewd stats.

$SLA_Effect_Devices	Devices
$SLA_Effect_DevicesDesc	Arousal increased by playing with devious devices
$SLA_Effect_DevicesHalfTime	Devices Rate
$SLA_Effect_DevicesHalfTimeDesc	Arousal reduction rate per hour after equipping a device.
$SLA_Effect_DevicesArousalOnEquip	Arousal on equip device
$SLA_Effect_DevicesArousalDesc	!Todo
$SLA_Effect_DevicesMin	Minimum arousal when bound
$SLA_Effect_DevicesMinDesc	!Todo
$SLA_Effect_DevicesPerDevice	Minimum arousal per device
$SLA_Effect_DevicesPerDeviceDesc	!Todo

$SLA_Effect_DDTeasing	Teasing
$SLA_Effect_DDTeasingDesc	Stimulation through devious devices



